so
good afternoon everyone i am adrika
and now it's finally time for our next
question
question number four of the day uh
so let's start with the question
so uh the question is that
you are feeling tired and drowsy while
driving
so in this type of situation what will
you do
a you will reach home and relax
be you will pull over your vehicle till
you are feeling
fine c take energy drink and
drink and drive or d take
medicine and drive so
uh so uh i will request everyone to
uh participate in this
you know this was our question and uh i
will request
every one of you to please answer this
kim ki
uh as we all know ki uh ha mariju indian
roads and
you know millions of us drive
all of us use these roads but still
these roads are not
safe and to make sure
that these roads they become safer we
can start with this simple step
[Music]
many lives of those people who are dying
every day uh
you know just as we talked about 415
people
die because of road crashes every day
and you can save them because awareness
follow and when you will start following
it
uh you know you will soon start driving
safely
and as you will start driving safely you
will save many lives also
and the uh and the third thing which is
like the one of the most
important or i'll say
which is that you can win some prizes
uh either a bike safety kit for you and
your family
or a car safety
[Music]
so i will once again repeat this
question uh you
feel tired and drowsy while driving
so in this situation what you will be
doing
uh the options are a reach home and
relax
b pull over your vehicle till you are
feeling fine
[Music]
continue
answer
first of all we can uh get
awareness we can save many lives of
people who are dying because
of road crashes and we can win some
prizes also
so andre you know it's really easy to
answer also
yeah it showed a step you know it does
not take a lot of time
each question is there for two hours uh
you know it doesn't take a lot of time
to
just answer a small question
and it's also really easy to answer
either you can answer this
with the help of the link in the
description box
or you can answer this from our youtube
page
or from our facebook page
so it's really simple and we all can
take this one
step ahead uh you know because
as we know that millions of people drive
on indian roads every day but 415 of
them
they die because of road crashes and
that is why
uh you know to save them to make our
uh to make our roads safer
we can start by taking this simple step
and that is to answer this question uh
the questions like these like right now
it is our fourth question
every day five questions will be coming
and they will be
in a gap of two hours so after every two
hours a new question will be coming
and and this is our fourth question of
the day
so so each question is valid also for
two hours
after two hours the question will be
closed and a new question will come
so so you know with this simple step
uh by answering all these questions
uh we can win prizes we can get
awareness
and we can also save lives of people
on the road you know you can become a
part of this campaign by
doing this you know what we are doing is
we are
trying to save lives of people who are
dying on indian roads
every day you know with this simple step
you can become a part of it
uh but with this simple step of
answering this
one question you can save lives of some
people
also
[Music]
415 people die because of road crashes
and hence uh to make our roads safer we
can take this simple step of
answering this question uh
and uh and we should also try to follow
these rules follow these road safety
rules follow these traffic
[Music]
uh
and when they have to follow it when
they see a traffic police
so uh which is not good and that is why
they must understand
[Music]
so i will request all of you to become a
part of this
and answer this question as well as the
other questions which will be coming
next
so today we will have question number
five after this
then the rest questions will be coming
tomorrow five questions will be coming
tomorrow also
so i will request all of you to become a
part of this
answer these questions which are coming
uh you know they are valid only for two
hours
and we can answer this it is really
simple to answer
uh so i will just once again
uh repeat this question so
you feel tired and drowsy while driving
uh so a you will
reach home and relax b
pull over your vehicle till you are
feeling fine
see take energy drink and drive
or d you will uh take a medicine
and then drive so you know it's really
simple to answer
as we talked about it's really simple to
answer
uh and you know
[Music]
and you know one of them who will be
answering the correct
answer of one of these questions will be
winning these
prizes either a bike safety kit
or a car safety kit so it's really
simple
uh so it's really simple you know every
every two hours new questions will be
coming
uh which are really easy to answer they
are valid they will be valid for two
hours five questions will be coming
every day and
[Music]
from our facebook page so
you know it's the easy answer
so we can uh we can simply become a part
of this
and the results uh the results uh
uh the results every day at 10 pm we
have a show called bluntly speaking
in that the results will be announced as
well as the answers also
the uh the results and answers both of
them
will be announced at the same time uh
in bluntly speaking at 10 pm
uh and also the results will be
shown on web page also so you can check
it from
anywhere uh either uh either you can
check
uh the results and answers from our show
or you can check the results from our
web page so i will request all of you to
please be a part of this
you know uh everyone wants to make our
routes
safer and it is really important to make
them
safe safe as we know okay
uh rose it lies because of road crashes
but still these roads they are not safe
or on a safe
so i will once again repeat the question
so you feel tired and drowsy while
driving
a reach home and relax
be pull over your vehicle
till you are feeling fine c
take energy drink and drive
or d take a medicine and drive
so i once again repeat it in hindi also
so
up uh up
or or you know
sleepy up while driving up
[Music]
so it's really simple to answer and
please
be a part of this you know i will
request all of you to please be a part
of this
involve more people also in this
video
um
so thank you so much everyone please be
a part of this
and uh thank you so much everyone
because with this simple step we can
save many
lives thank you